[
  {
    "correcta": true,
    "id": 1,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 1",
    "respuesta": "40 km/h",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 2,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 2",
    "respuesta": "Botiquín de primeros auxilios",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 3,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 3",
    "respuesta": "100 metros",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 4,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 4",
    "respuesta": "Prohibición",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 5,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 5",
    "respuesta": "Cambiar de carril",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 6,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 6",
    "respuesta": "Continuar sin detenerse",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 7,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 7",
    "respuesta": "0.08%",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 8,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 8",
    "respuesta": "Adelantar con precaución",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 9,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 9",
    "respuesta": "100 km/h",
    "tiempo": 2
  },
  {
    "correcta": false,
    "id": 10,
    "pregunta": "Pregunta 10",
    "respuesta": "1 metro",
    "tiempo": 2
  }
]